* 

* Security Awareness

* Resources

Privacy Policy for Hut 6 Security Limited
=========================================

### Who we are

We are Hut 6 Security Limited (henceforth referred to as ‘the Company’), a company registered in England and Wales. Company Number: 10447061.

Registered Office: Platfform, 11 Devon Place, Newport, Wales, NP20 4NW.

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please feel free to email us at privacy@hutsix.io or send a letter to the address above.

### Scope of this Policy

This privacy policy is intended for the users and visitors of the Company’s website at https://www.hutsix.io and is separate to the privacy policy for the software services offered by the Company. This policy also covers select surveys that are distributed by the Company. These surveys will link directly to this privacy policy.

From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy and we encourage you to review this periodically. We will keep previous versions of this privacy policy, which are available on request.

If there is a significant change to the privacy policy and you have provided an email address to us, then we will notify you via email in advance of the change coming into effect.

### What personal data we collect and why we collect it

#### Contact forms

If you complete a contact form on our site, we will collect and store all of the information that you submitted in the form. We will use the information provided to address your query and may respond using the email address provided.

Contact forms may also have an option to be included in marketing or other types of emails. If you select this option, then the name and email address you provided will be added to the relevant mailing list.

The lawful basis we rely upon for processing this information is your consent. You are able to remove your consent at any time. You can do this by contacting privacy@hutsix.io.

#### Surveys

If you complete a survey on this site, by e-mail or through SurveyMonkey, the information you enter will be collected and stored for the purpose of market research. We will not use your information for any other purposes without your consent.

Market research includes analysing and evaluating your responses in order to understand needs, preferences, opinions, experience with products and services, assessing future opportunities and to monitor market performance. This information will be used by Hut Six internally and, unless otherwise stated, may also be compiled in the form of reports and whitepapers that will be used as freely available content on the HutSix.io website. Responses to questions will be used anonymously, with no identifying information regarding the person providing it or the company they work for being disclosed without the written consent of the individual and company.

We will only retain names, emails and other personally identifiable information for as long as is required to complete the research, unless consent has been obtained to retain them.

Surveys may have an option to be contacted via email or phone for marketing purposes. Should you consent to further communication, the details you provide will be stored within Hut Six’s customer relationship management system (CRM) system, in HubSpot, for use in marketing communications via email and telephone correspondence regarding Hut Six’s product offering.

Surveys may have an option to receive free digital media such as posters, whitepapers and guides. Should you consent to receiving one or more of these, then your information will be entered into the Hut Six CRM for this sole purpose. Upon delivery of the requested collateral, your information will be removed from the system.

The lawful basis we rely upon for processing this information is your consent. You are able to remove your consent at any time. You can do this by contacting privacy@hutsix.io.

We use SurveyMonkey to collect information for some surveys. You can view their privacy policy at https://www.surveymonkey.com/mp/legal/privacy-policy/

#### Marketing & Analytics

Our website uses Google Analytics 4 and HubSpot to track your usage of this website. You can read about how Google processes this information here: https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites

This data may be combined with information we receive from Google Ads to allow us to improve our marketing campaigns.

The lawful basis for the processing of this data is consent. You can change your privacy preferences by [clicking here](https://www.hutsix.io/).

#### Logs

We collect information about your device’s requests to the website. This includes your IP address, the page requested and the browser you are using.

We collect this information for security purposes and to block malicious users from the website.

This information will be retained for no longer than one month, unless your device is believed to have been used to attack the website. In this case we may retain the data for as long as is necessary.

The lawful basis we rely upon for processing this information is legitimate interest.

### Where we send your data

#### HubSpot, Inc.

HubSpot are a company specialising in marketing and sales software. We use HubSpot as a Data Processor to help us manage mailing lists, send marketing emails and track sales leads. Your information is stored in HubSpot if you complete a Contact form (excluding the support contact form).

The information stored in HubSpot may include your name, email address, phone number, place of work and any other information provided in the Contact form. This information may be supplemented by other details provided by you over email, phone or in-person. Google Analytics and Google Ads data is shared with HubSpot to help us improve our marketing efforts.

If you have consented to analytics, we also use the HubSpot prospects tracking tool to detect your IP address which we may use to determine the organisation associated that IP address so we can learn more about the visitors to our site. We can use this to identify what types of businesses are visiting our site to better help us market our product to them.

HubSpot is located in the USA.

#### Google

##### G-Suite

Contact form submissions may forwarded to and replied to from an email address managed by Google’s GSuite product.

##### Google Analytics

Our website uses Google Analytics 4 to track your usage of the site. You can read about how Google processes this information here: https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites

##### Google Ads

If you arrived at https://hutsix.io by clicking on an advert your behaviour on the site will be analysed in google analytics as well to help us better understand our marketing spend. You can read about how Google processes this information here: https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites

#### Microsoft

We use Microsoft Office 365 for internal IT services. Your information is only stored in these services if you complete a Contact form. The data is stored within the UK.

#### CloudAlly

We use CloudAlly for backups of our data storage. As such information that is stored within Microsoft services will also be processed by CloudAlly. The data is stored in the UK, and CloudAlly itself is based in Israel which is recognised as providing an adequate level of data protection by the European Commission and by the UK Government.

#### Visit Digital (Visit Digital Ltd.)

Visit Digital help us improve and optimise our Website Experience by assisting us in analysing how people use the website.

#### Web Marketer (Web Marketer Ltd.)

Web Marketer help us improve and optimise our Paid Marketing and Website Experience by assisting us in analysing how people interact with our ads and the website.

#### Automattic (Aut O’Mattic A8C Ireland Ltd.)

We use the Akismet service from Automattic to check form submissions for spam.

### What rights you have over your data

Under data protection law, you have rights including:

* Access – You have the right to ask us for copies of your personal information.
* Rectification – You have the right to ask us to rectify information you think is inaccurate. You also have the right to ask us to complete information you think is incomplete.
* Erasure – You have the right to ask us to erase your personal information in certain circumstances.
* Restriction of processing – You have the right to ask us to restrict the processing of your information in certain circumstances.
* Object to processing – You have the the right to object to the processing of your personal data in certain circumstances.
* Data portability – You have the right to ask that we transfer the information you gave us to another organisation, or to you, in certain circumstances.
* You are not required to pay any charge for exercising your rights. If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. Please contact us at privacy@hutsix.io if you wish to make a request.

You also have the right to object to the processing of your information, and the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority. The supervisory authority in the United Kingdom is the Information Commissioner’s Office who can be contacted at https://ico.org.uk/concerns/ or telephone: 0303 123 1113.

### EU Representative

We have appointed IT Governance Europe Limited to act as our EU Representative If you wish to exercise your rights under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), or have any queries in relation to your rights or privacy matters generally please email our Representative at eurep@itgovernance.eu or post your request or query to: EU Representative, IT Governance Europe, Third Floor, The Boyne Tower, Bull Ring, Lagavooren, Drogheda, Co. Louth, A92 F682.

When contacting our Representative please ensure you include our company name in any correspondence.

**Company**

Hut 6 Security Limited  
Platfform  
Devon Place  
Newport  
NP20 4NW

T: +44 (0) 330 223 0182  
E: info@hutsix.io

**Security awareness**

**Company**

© Copyright 2024 Hut 6 Security Limited.

Hut Six is the trading name of Hut 6 Security Limited, a Company Registered in England and Wales.  
Registration Number: 10447061  
VAT Number: 277 2052 03
